福克斯探照灯影业
TSG娱乐
水型物语
If I spoke about it...
If I did...
What would I tell you...
I wonder?
Would I tell you about the time...?
It happened a long time ago, it seems...
In the last days of a fair prince's reign.
Or would I tell you about the place?
A small city near the coast...
But far from everything else.
Or... i don't know...
Would I tell you about her?
The princess without voice.
Or perhaps I would just warn you...
About the truth of these facts...
And the tale of love and loss...
And the monster...
Who tried to destroy it all.
I have sinned.
I've offended the god.
I'm deep in sin, my lord Hedak.
Let me judge of that.
I've doubted the ceremony of the sacrifice.
I don't wanna go upstairs.
Why, everybody's got to go upstairs, miss Lloyd,
If they wants to go to bed.
The sirens wake you up?
It was a fire. The chocolate factory.
Could you smell that?
Oh, my. Toasted cocoa.
Tragedy and delight... hand in hand.
Oh, my dear child.
I would waste away if you weren't here looking after me.
I am the proverbial starving...
Oh, watch this.
It's bojangles. The stair dance.
Oh, that's so hard.
Cagney did it. Different but beautiful.
I wanna do that too.
All right.
- Are you ready? - Yup.
Come on.
Ah!
Say, you catch on quick.
Elisa!
Next time you come to bring the rent...
I want you to stay and see the bible movie, eh?
Okay, I have two free tickets here.
You bring your neighbor giles. He's a good boy.
Bible movie and comedy. Nobody's going to the theater, huh?
I-I throw in a free popcorn and soda!
Oh, no, burgassi, there's two s's there!
Come on!
Two s's, mardi grass! Mardi grass!
All personnel, be advised that sector 12.
Has now been cleared to level a-c
Elisa!
Come on! I'm here already.
You gotta learn to be on time.
Hey, what you doing?
- Don't cut in, dummy! - Leave her alone, woman.
I was keeping her place.
I get reported, I come after you and the mute.
You do that, yolanda.
You do that.
Ugh.
My feet are already killin' me.
I made brewster pigs in a blanket tonight before leavin'.
And boy, he just ate 'em up.
No thank you's, no yum yums. Not a peep.
Man is as silent as a grave.
But if farts were flattery,
Honey, he'd be shakespeare.
Then I get home and I make him breakfast.
Eggs, bacon, and buttered toast.
I butter the man's toast, elisa.
Mm-hmm, both sides. As if he was a child.
And I don't even get a "thank you."
You'd be grateful.
Because you're an educated woman.
But my brewster? All he had going for him.
Was animal magnetism back in the day.
Hadn't worked in a while.
What in the sam hill?
Lou!
You boys mind putting the trash in the can?
That's what it's there for.
Hard to believe, huh? That's what it's there for.
All right, all right. Sorry zelda. Sorry.
I don't know what they're doin'.
Makin' a goddamn mess is what I'd say...
Zelda!
- Stop the chatter please. - Yes, sir.
And there's no call for the blasphemy.
Sorry, mr. Fleming, sir.
Mhmm, a moment of your time.
Today, we are receiving a new team and asset here in t-4.
This is dr. Robert hoffstetler from
our sister facility bolster or..
Now, I don't want to bolster or...
Overstate the matter but...
This may very well be the most sensitive asset.
Ever to be housed in this facility.
- How was your trip? - Fine.
- Who's security here? - Just one moment, please.
Security! Who's security?
Welcome to the t-4, sir.
I'm fleming, head of security.
Any questions you have or concerns you can refer to me.
Understand? I'll be in charge from now on.
Get them out.
Help me move the cylinder into the compressor.
Bring it here, bring it here.
Bring it over here.
We need to pressurize it immediately.
Elisa, elisa!
Come on.
Lord, what goes on in this place?
Did you see that?
Yes, I'm wearing the hairpiece. How's it look?
Oh, careful, the car.
It's not a hairpiece, it's a toupee. It's French.
It's eternal, see?
Tantalus never achieved the escape of death.
'Cause the fruit on the branches
was just always out of his reach.
And the water in the stream receded every time.
Stooped down to drink.
And so, that's why we say things today, like...
Look at those tantalizing pies.
Thank you. You'll come back now, you hear?
Yes, pies for breakfast. Just trust me on this.
Hey, folks, welcome to dixie doug's.
I've seen you in here before, right?
Yes, I've been here a couple of times, as a matter of fact.
Partial to key lime pie?
I am, I am. Two to go.
Just go with it, please, please.
Uh, I uh, it's a craving that I indulge in.
It can't possibly be good for me but nothing I like is.
No, no, it's a mighty fine pie, key lime.
You wouldn't happen to be the uh,
Famous dixie doug himself, would you?
Heck, no. Pies are trucked throughout the country.
They call it uh, "franchising", see?
Oh.
They give us the spinners, the signage.
That there's "pie boy", our mascot.
I don't talk like that. I'm from ottawa.
No.
I completely bought it.
"That's-a great-a pie."
The...
The uh, the little-little guy. Is he supposed to be italian?
I guess so.
That was very clever.
You'll come back now, you hear?
"You'll come back now."
Do you think he meant it?
He had noticed me. I mean, you s... you heard that.
This pie is rather sordid.
Don't spit it out.
Next time we go, we'll just try a different flavor.
Hmm?
Save it for later. For the wait.
The clocks point to 6 a.m. eastern standard time.
The skies are beginning to lighten.
And a cool north wind rustles across the...
Groups of negroes have been
swarming in front.
Oh, dear god, change that awfulness.
I do not want to see that.
I do not want to see it.
That's better, that's better.
Oh, look at betty!
Oh, to be young and beautiful.
If I could go back...
To when I was 18...
I didn't know anything about anything...
I'd give myself a bit of advice.
I would say,
Take better care of your teeth and fuck.
A lot more.
Oh, no, no, that's very good advice.
Will you look at this?
Look.
Some of the best minds in the country.
Peeing all over the floor in this here facility.
Mm-mm-mm.
There's pee freckles on the ceilin' there!
How'd they get it up there?
Just how big a target do they need, you figure?
They get enough practice that's for sure.
My brewster...
No one's ever called him a great mind.
But...
Even he manages to hit the can seventy percent of the time.
- Excuse us, sir. - No, no, no. That's all right.
Go ahead.
You ladies seem to be chatting enjoyably.
Girl talk no doubt.
Don't mind me.
Elisa...
Look, don't touch.
That lovely dingus right there is an alabama howdy-do.
Molded grip handle.
Low-current, high-voltage electric shock cattle prod.
Name's strickland. Security.
Fleming's security.
Ha!
Oh, no, no. A man washes his hands.
Before or after tending to his needs.
It tells you a lot about a man.
He does it both times...
Points to a weakness in character.
Ladies.
It was very pleasant chatting with you both.
Short people are mean.
I never met a short man that
stayed nice all.
No, sir.
Mean little backstabbers, all of 'em.
Maybe it's the air down there.
Not enough oxygen or somethin'.
Hmm.
Help! He's losing blood!
Help!
Come on, come on.
You think the russians broke in?
I don't think so. And if they did...
Duane's meatloaf will kill them all, honey.
It was two shots. D'you hear 'em?
All right, three.
And that scream.
Lord, whatever happens in this place.
You two, come with me.
Right now? Mr. fleming, sir?
Any chance we could... conclude our dinner?
Now.
Oh, heavens to betsy. We are in a pickle.
We are in such a pickle.
You will have exactly 20 minutes.
To render this-this lab immaculate.
And so on and so forth. 20 minutes.
It's a lot of blood. What went on in here?
I can handle pee.
I can handle poo.
But blood, mm.
Blood just does somethin' to me.
Here, honey... help me mop it up.
The sooner we get outta here, the better.
Is that a tater tot?
Oh!
It's a finger.
It's two fingers, okay.
Okay, okay. Put 'em away, and... just wait here.
I'm gonna get mr. Fleming.
Where are these body parts?
The body parts?
No, I believe you, honey. Are you sure it was alive?
Because I saw a mermaid once in a carnival tent.
And it was a monkey.
Sewn to the tail of a fish. Looked real to me!
All right, I apologize.
I have a deadline.
You know, uh...
Corn flakes were invented to prevent masturbation.
Didn't work.
Oh, alice faye just started.
She was a huge star, huge.
And one day, she couldn't take the
bullshit and the backstabbing anymore.
She just walked away from it all.
Ta-da.
It's not bad, is it?
For being shit.
Uh, listen, you eat, you go to bed, you rest.
And when i... get paid...
We get pie.
No, we don't get pie. I get pie.
You get whatever you want.
Wish me luck.
Green.
They want the gelatin to be green now.
- I was told red. - New concept.
That's the future now. Green.
Oh, and they want the... them happier, the family.
- Happier? Happier? - Mm.
The father looks like he just
discovered the missionary position.
Giles!
Well, uh, what are they supposed to be happy about?
The client wanted photographs. I sold them on this.
It's too bad. This is nice work.
It is nice, isn't it? I think it's one of my best.
How you holdin' up?
- You drinking? - No.
Not a drop. No.
Getting any work since you left klein & saunders?
You mean since I was asked to leave by you.
We are not getting into this now.
I want to come back, bernie.
We'll see.
Now do this.
Good work.
Elisa!
What are you doing in there?
Cleaning, huh.
Listen, honey.
Mr. "I pee with my hands on my hips" wants to see us both.
Zelda d. Fuller.
How long have you two known each other, zelda?
Uh, about ten years, sir.
No siblings, zelda?
No, sir.
That's not common, is it? For your people?
My momma died after me.
After I was born.
What does that "d" stand for?
Delilah... sir.
On account of the bible.
Delilah, she betrayed samson.
Lulled him to sleep. Cut his hair.
Philistines tortured him, humiliated him.
Burned his eyes out.
Guess my momma didn't read the good book close enough.
And you...
Elisa... esposito.
Doesn't Esposito mean orphanage?
Oh, our lady of sorrows orphanage in putnam.
They found her by the river... in the water.
It was you that found my fingers.
Oh.
Thanks.
Three hours in surgery.
They rebuilt the first phalanx here.
Sutured the tendons.
Don't know if it's gonna take or not.
There was mustard on them.
- A paper bag? - It was all we had, sir.
I answer mostly, on account that she can't talk.
She can't? She deaf?
Mute, sir.
She said she can hear you.
Oh, those scars on your neck.
That's what did it. Cut your voice box, right?
She said since she was a baby.
Who would do that to a baby?
The world is sinful.
Do you say so, delilah?
Well, let me say this upfront.
You clean that lab. You get out.
The thing we keep in there, is an affront.
Do you know what an affront is, zelda?
Something offensive.
That's right. And I should know, I dragged that...
Filthy thing...
Out of the river muck in south america all the way here.
And along the way, we didn't get to like each other much.
Now... you may think...
That thing looks human.
Stands on two legs, right?
But, we're created in the lord's image.
You don't think that's what the Lord looks like, do you?
I wouldn't know, Sir. What the Lord looks like.
Well, human, zelda. He looks like a human. Like me.
Or even you.
Maybe a little more like me, I guess.
Well, that's all.
General hoyt. Thank you for calling me back, sir.
- Feeling better? - Oh, yes, sir, much better.
- Pain pills, is all. - You lost two fingers, was it?
Two fingers, yeah. He got two fingers.
But I still got my thumb, my trigger and my pussy finger.
Sounds to me like you'll be all right then.
Yes, sir, that's right. Looking forward to your visit, sir.
Decisions need to be made about the asset.
Some fruity pies await you.
Three new locations in downtown baltimore.
The future is here.
Get some rest.
Pick me up at nine thrity
twenty one hundred and thrity hours. Yes, sir.
Dixie dougs. That's-a great-a pie.
I'm home.
I made you an omelette.
- Hey, dad. Guess what? - No pancakes?
I've gone through half the boxes,
and I can't find out the griddle.
Guess what?
I made you cheese and broccoli omelette.
How're you feeling? Does it hurt?
- A little bit. Pills help. - Guess what?
- What? - We are burying a time capsule.
At the new school. I wanted to ask you.
Do you think we'll all have jet packs?
- In the future? - Believe it, son.
Oh, bus is here.
This is america.
- Bye, dad. - Bye, dad.
Finish you omelette then wash your hands real good.
And come upstairs, sweetie.
I kinda like it here. The kids like the lawn.
Plus, D.C. is just half an hour away, isn't it?
It is still Baltimore, Elaine. No one likes Baltimore.
You know what I'm thinkin'?
I'm thinkin'... i need a new car.
You need a new car, do you?
How about a cadillac, mister?
Richard.
Oh.
Oh, richard.
Uh.
Oh. Uh.
Oh.
Swee... sweetie?
Sweetie, you're um...
Your-your hand, it's bleeding.
Silence, stop talking.
Don't talk. I want you in silence.
Silent. Silent.
Yes... yes, silence.
Dr. levinson. Aeronautics. Dr. levinson. Aeronautics.
- On the window... - what?!
The sparrow...!
Nests... on the window... sill!
- And the eagle takes the prey! - What?!
Elisa, hurry, hurry. Come on.
Sweet god, girl.
You're doing it again, zelda.
Oh, give it a rest, yolanda.
Oh!
Whew!
Hey, zelda, want a smoke?
- That shit ain't good for you, duane.
- Yeah, but I feel good.
It does, doesn't it?
Come on, elisa, just one.
Come on, come on, come on.
Don't worry about that camera. We push him up at break time.
- Mmhmm. - This here's a blind spot.
Fleming, I have to finish some things in here.
Fetch mcdonald, will ya?
Aw, you miss me, huh?
I took a candy break.
This is what scares you, huh?
Gee, you should be used to it by now.
There you go again, makin' that god-awful sound.
Is that you cryin', huh? Is that what it is?
Are you hurtin'?
Or maybe...
You're angry?!
Maybe you'd like to get another bite, huh? Go ahead.
Huh?!
I can't tell!
I mean, are you beggin'?
'Cause to me, it's just the worst
fucking noise I've ever heard.
Paging captain walters.
Captain walters. Please pick up the courtesy phone.
Elisa...
Elisa?
General hoyt! Welcome, sir.
Everything's ready. Glad to have you, sir.
- Good to see you, son. - Thank you.
Good god almighty. Is that it?
Hell of a lot bigger than I thought.
Ugly as sin.
You know, the natives in the
amazon worship him as the god.
Doesn' t look like much of a God right now, does it?
Well, they were primitives, sir.
You know, they would toss offerings into the water.
Flowers, fruits, crap like that.
Then they tried to stop the oil drill with bows and arrows.
That didn't turn out too well.
He's bleeding.
What happened?
It's an animal, Hoffstetler. Just keepin' it tame.
What the hell have we got here, son?
This creature, sir...
It can alternate between two entirely
separate breath
- mudskipper can do that. - No.
Look, you want to put a man in space.
He's gonna have to endure conditions
the human body just wasn't made for.
This gives us an edge against the soviets.
How long can it breathe outside the water?
The reality is, sir, we don't
know jackshit about this thing.
Well, the soviets want it. We know that much.
Those cockeyed bastards.
You know, we let them send a dog up into space...
And we get a good laugh.
Then the next thing you know, they send a human up.
A ruskie, orbiting the planet, doing god knows what?
Who's laughing then? Krushchev, that's who.
We let him put a dog up into space...
And he laughs then puts a commie up in space.
And he laughs, and then he puts missiles into cuba.
Have we learned nothing?
Sir, we need to get him back in the water.
See, these scientists, they're like artists, sir.
They fall in love with their playthings.
Now, right here, see, along the middle?
This creature has a thick, jointed cartilage.
That separates the primary and secondary lungs.
Am I explaining this correctly, bob?
Yes, but we have
-been able to determine...
-it makes the x-ray.
In principle, sir, yes, but...
- there are ways of... - now, I believe, if we wanna.
Get the edge on the soviets, we need to vivisect this thing.
No, no.
- Take it apart, learn how it works. - No.
No! That would defeat the purpose!
Sir, he's passed out, please.
Put him in the tank! Let him pressurize.
General hoyt, sir!
You cannot, under any circumstance, kill this creature.
Count these stars with me, son.
There're five of 'em.
Means I can do whatever the hell I want.
Now, you wanna plead your case? I'll listen to it.
But at the end of the day...
It is my damn decision.
So crack the damn thing open.
Learn what you can and close up shop here.
And give yourself a good pat on the back, strickland.
- You've done it. - Thank you, sir.
Now, hurry up and finish the job, son.
Absolutely, sir.
Get him out? What are you talking about?
No, absolutely not.
Because it's breaking the law, that's why.
Probably breaking the law just talking about it.
Oh, he's alone? Oh.
Now, does this mean that...
Whenever we go to a chinese restaurant,
You want to save every fish in the tank?
So what if he's alone?
We're all alone.
"The loneliest thing you've ever seen."
Well, you just said it, right, you just said it.
You called it a "thing." it's a thing. It's a freak.
I can understand you.
Calm down.
God, calm d...
All right, I-i will repeat it to you.
"What am I?"
"I move my mouth."
"like him."
"I make no sound."
"what does that make me?"
"all that I am..."
"all that I've ever been..."
"brought me here"
"to him."
See, you're saying "him." it's a "him" now.
It's a h...
Ah! You just hit me.
Elisa, let go of me.
I'm looking, I'm looking. You've never... hit me!
"When he looks at me..."
"the way he looks at me..."
"he does not know..."
"what I lack..."
"or..."
"how..."
"I am incomplete."
"he... sees me..."
"for what i... am..."
"as I am."
"he's happy."
"to see me."
"every time."
"everyday."
"now..."
"I can... either..."
"save him..."
"or let him die."
Okay.
I'm leaving.
I have to... I have to leave.
Just, elisa, please stop.
Listen to me, just listen to me.
I have to go.
I have to... I'm leaving now because this...
Elisa, this is very important to me.
This is a second chance for me.
I'm sorry, but I have to go.
Oh, god.
When I come back,
We just will not talk about this ever again.
Elisa, there's...
Oh, all right.
What are we? What are you and I?
Do you know what we are? We are nothing.
Nothing. We can do nothing.
I'm sorry.
But this, this, this is just...
Oh, god, It's not even human.
God.
What?
Giles!
I've been waiting.
- I know, sorry. - It's okay.
We going in?
You should've just mailed the art.
No. I want to show it to you and the team in person.
I think It's some of my best work.
And It's green as can be.
It's uh, It's not a good time.
Maybe later.
Oh, well, sure. No problem.
What would be a good time for you, Bernie?
You painted that?
Yeah.
Wowee.
You're good.
Well, apparently, not as good as a photograph.
But it is good, isn't it?
I couldn't paint anything like that.
Here... on me.
For me?
We don't get many like you in here.
You seem... very educated.
I like talkin' to you.
The-the thing is, that's the...
The only reason that I come in here is...
The conversation! And...
The pie is mighty fine too, isn't it?
Yeah. Yeah.
It's no key lime, but... It's good.
You know I work alone...
And uh...
My best friend's not much of a conversationalist.
You see, that's part of being the job here, It's like...
Being a bartender.
You serve people pie, you listen to their problems.
You get to know 'em.
I'd like to get to know you better.
The hell are you doing, old man?
Oh, o-o-oh.
Hey, no, no, no. Not the counter.
Take out only. You can't sit there.
You want something, you order, you take it out.
But It's empty... the-the counter's empty...
They're all reserved all day. You don't sit down.
Y'all come back now, y'hear?
You didn't need to talk to them like that.
You should go too.
And don't come back. This is a family restaurant.
I have no one.
And you are the only person that I can talk to.
Now...
Whatever this thing is...
You need it.
So...
You just tell me what to do.
All hope fades...
As the spring recedes. Let's go.
Cadillac deville. Best car ever made.
V8, 390 cid, clean and crisp like a fresh dollar bill.
- I'm just idling around. - And I'm just talking.
Am radio, air conditioner, power windows, power brakes,
Power steering, power seats...
All deluxe interior appointment choices.
143 options. Now this...
It's the taj-mahal on wheels.
Hm.
I'm not sure about the green.
No, It's not green, my friend. Teal.
- Well, teal looks green to me. - But it isn't, see?
It's a limited edition. Twelve coats of paint.
Polished by hand. All authentic chrome detailing.
Four out of five successful men in America drive a Cadillac.
- Is that a fact? - This here is the future.
And you strike me as a man who is headed there.
- Where? - Why, the future.
You're the man of the future.
You belong in this car.
Wow!
Sir, that is a-that is a beautiful car!
It's uh...
What can I say? You gotta feel good drivin' that, huh?
And what a wonderful shade of green, huh?
Teal.
- Tomorrow... - Mmm?
- I'll make a melaleuca meatloaf. - Mm-hmm..
Just for you, extra raisins.
So at 5:00 a.m. I drive my car down the loading ramp.
And uh, the shifts are changing and I...
How much time do I have?
Five minutes? I'll remember, yeah,
Five a.m., five minutes, five-five, five-five.
So, y-you're gonna move the cameras, right.
And uh, I'm gonna be synchronizing our watches.
Just like they do in the movies.
Oh, god, I'm so proud of you.
God! You just-you're not afraid!
You are? Very?
Don't tell me that. I'm terrified.
I think this is some of my best work.
"Michael Parker" is a good
trustworthy name. It's a little butch.
Yes, age fifty-one.
Fifty four.
You don't have to be rude.
Fifty... seven.
I put the hair on. I can pull it off.
I can wear this or I ha.
Oh, go, go, off, off, off, off. Go, go.
Or I have this. Now this...
This I think it says, "working man."
But this, now this, this says...
This says, with the butterscotch tie...
This says, "casual" but still stylish.
So... you like this? I agree. I agree.
I think we're ready.
Mr. Strickland!
Sally, could you call Miss Esposito to clean up a spill?
You know, I can't figure it out myself.
You're not much to look at, but...
Go figure.
I keep thinking about you.
And when you say you're mute, are you entirely silent, or...
Do you squawk a little?
Some mutes squawk. Not pretty... hmm?
I just want you to know...
I don't mind those scars.
I don't mind that you can't speak, either.
When you come right down to it...
I like it.
A lot.
Kind of gets me going.
I bet I can make you squawk a little.
Hey, honey, you okay?
Hurry up, I want to be home early.
My feet are killing me.
We need to delay the procedure.
Knock before you enter my office.
This is urgent!
Go back out. Knock.
Then I'll let you in and we'll talk.
That's the protocol. Follow the protocol.
Come in.
I...
Could you get the door for me, please?
See? That's the way. Now we talk.
I need more time.
Don't let the fact that you feel like a loser now,
That you let your competitive tendency...
I'm not competitive!
I don't want an intricate, beautiful thing destroyed.
This thing dies. You learn. I leave.
Outta here. I settle down.
My family settles down. Somewhere nice. A real city.
This creature is intelligent.
Capable of language...
Of understanding emotions.
So are the soviets, the gooks.
And we still kill them, don't we?
The bottom line is, this isn't a petting zoo.
And I don't want to be in this
shithole any longhe investigation.
Do you?
Bob...
No, I don't.
Hey, what are you waiting for?
Have you seen Elisa?
Come on, Zelda.
Did you move the camera? On the loading dock?
Is that where you're taking him?
Through the service tunnel?
That's very smart.
Who do you work for?
This water must be kept at five to eight percent salinity.
Table salt will do.
Mix one of these in his water every three days.
Raw protein diet is a must.
In five minutes, I'll meet you at the loading dock.
The lights will go out, so be prepared.
M-mr. Strickland, sir...
Twelve hours to the vivisection of the asset, and to...
I-I need your signature here, please.
Hold it right there.
Michael parker. Is that you?
My whole life.
Are you out of your mind?
Don't do this, Elisa.
Don't do this!
What's that... what's that vehicle?
Uh, gosh, sir, I'm not sure, It's... a laundry van?
B-but it's-it's not scheduled.
Sir!
- Meet me at the loading dock. - Sir!
- Sir, what do you need me to... - Get backup.
Step out of the vehicle, sir.
Oh, god, I'm not good at this.
Out of the vehicle, now!
I will not say it again.
- God, please don't shoot me. - Get out!
Oh, god, don't shoot me.
What are you waiting for? We're out of time.
Get out now!
We have to go. Hurry!
Oh, woman, we're gonna burn in hell!
Come on, push!
Push!
I swear I'm not doing this on purpose.
Mechanical objects and I just don't get along!
What?
She's waiting for you at the dock.
- Go! Now! - Okay, hold on.
Who's that man? I think he just killed someone.
Oh!
Oh, my god, oh, my god!
Are we ready? Are we ready?
He's so beautiful.
Did I do that?
I'm just not good at this.
Move! Move!
No...
No!
Salt? What are you talking about? Salt.
Elisa!
Israeli "popper."
Smell the magnesium?
The Russians hate the Jews,
but can't get enough of their gadgets.
How'd they get in here?
Oh, uh, forged id, painted plates,
and uh, so on.
And they moved the main video camera on the dock, sir.
Well, no one has to know. We got 24 hours before I bounce it up.
I called it in.
- You called it in? - The moment it happened, I-I-I...
Mr. Strickland, sir.
What is it, Sally?
Sir, General Hoyt is on the phone.
That thing was our space dog, Strickland.
- You know that. - Sir, I'm getting it back.
I don't... I can't be in a negative frame of mind, sir.
So you're feeling good?
Feeling strong. Getting it back.
You can get it done. You're gonna get it done.
For me, son. For me.
That's when you're planning on releasing him?
On the tenth?
So what if the rains are late?
What happens with the canal?
All right.
What's that?
Let me see it.
Is that for me?
Yeah. That's good. Keep that up.
Lookin' like you don't know anything.
Lord help me if they ask me if I do.
I'm not a good liar.
Except to Brewster.
It takes a lotta lies to keep a marriage goin'.
All personel. Prepare to present your identity and clearance cards.
Lord. What in the...
You've got us in a lot of troubles.
My opinion, we're looking at a highly trained group, sir.
I'm thinking, conceivably, sir...
Special forces or so on so forth.
Red army special forces?
Conceivably. I-I mean, they're highly-trained.
Well-financed. An elite group.
Highly efficient. Ruthless. Clockwork precision.
Infiltration took less than five minutes, sir.
My conservative estimate is that this was a strike force
of at least ten men.
Have you always been alone?
Did you ever have someone?
Do you know what happened to you? Do you?
Because I don't. I don't know what happened to me.
I-I don't know.
I look in the mirror and the only thing that I recognize.
Are these eyes.
In this old man's face.
You know, sometimes I think
I was either born too early or too late for my life.
Maybe we're both just relics.
Security measures have been increased to maximum levels.
Prepare to present your identity and clearance cards.
Sir. Got them.
Oh, zelda, elisa.
Looks like you two punched out before the incident.
Still...
If you know something about what transpired here...
It's your obligation... to report.
Any detail no matter how small or trivial it may seem.
Trivial means unimportant.
I didn't see nothin' out of the ordinary, no.
Or trivial.
See, my feet were hurtin'.
What about you?
She didn't see anything.
Hoffstetler. Dr. hoffstetler...
Did either of you see him coming in or out of the lab?
He works there... doesn't he?
I mean in a different way. Doing something different.
Something trivial?
No, sir.
What am I doing?
Interviewing the fucking help.
The shit cleaners.
The piss wipers.
You two, go ahead. Leave.
What'd you say to me?
What is she saying?
I... i didn't catch it.
What is she saying?!
She-she is saying "thank you."
Next.
I didn't see you last night.
Or the night before.
I'm sorry, ed, but now that I'm
spending all day on the office
Carol feels that I should spend my evenings with her.
Well, if you spend the evenings with her,
When will I see you?
There's only one thing left to do.
Volunteer.
No, no, no, no, no!
I want to get home early.
Brewster's been in a bad mood lately.
Holy Jesus!
What are you doing standing in the shadows.
Of the women's locker room?
They may be watching me and there are no cameras here.
For good reason.
What if you caught us at an inconvenient moment?
I need to know that he's all right.
- He is. - When will you release him?
Soon.
When the rains fills the canal that flows to the sea.
If you need anything.
Release him soon.
What did she say?
She said, you are a good man, Dr. Hoffstetler.
My name is dimitri.
Honored to meet you.
Hey, dummy, phone call for you. It's urgent.
Don't worry about me. I'm fine.
Believe me, I'm fine.
He ate pandora. Wasn't his fault.
He's a wild creature.
We can't ask him to be anything else.
Elisa, go find him.
Go. Go!
Go.
You're lucky.
I stayed awake as long as I could.
But, you know, I'm not even young man anymore.
Is he all right? You sure?
Where you going?
No, no.
Okay, don't-no, no. Don't play with the kitties. No, no.
Don't play with the kitties.
I'm not-i'm not angry. I'm not...
You did that, but it's okay. Ooh,
I don't think that's sanitary.
Enough.
Interesting guy.
Prepare to present your identity and clearance cards.
You wanted to see me?
How's it going? The investigation?
Well, we have a promising lead.
Really?
That's good to hear.
You joined us in galveston, but.
Where were you before, hoffstetler?
Doctor.
- Excuse me? - Doctor hoffstetler.
Protocol.
Wisconsin. Madison.
Oh, that's right. You gave up a
tenure track position, didn't you?
Gave it all up... for us.
I suppose...
you are getting ready to leave us now, then, huh?
Only it the creature isn't found.
Well, what do you think? You think we will find it?
Well, you said you had a lead.
I do.
Why you smiling, hon?
Stop looking like that.
What happened?
Why?
How?
Does he... have a...?
Lord!
Never trust a man.
Even when he looks flat down there.
You rang?
Oh, hi, peter, I just signed up for anthropology.
We're gonna hold class in the
amazon jungle in South America.
South america? Ooh, man.
You're gonna have to get up awful early in the morning.
That's a long hike.
No, peter, we're gonna stay down there.
We are?
Oh, no, you're not coming along too.
This is a gelatin parfait.
You're gonna love it.
Dad, can we watch bonanza?
Bonanza is much too violent.
Do you know what I was thinking today?
We get the kids a p-u-p-p-y.
What is going on?!
I've got water pouring into my theater!
I have four paying customers, I can't afford a refund.
It's probably a pipe. I'll take care of it.
You don't fix it, no more rent room.
I will fix it.
Elisa!
Dear god.
I'm toweling my hair!
It's my hair.
Oh, look at my arm.
The wound! It's like it was never there. Look at that.
You said that...
He was worshipped like a god.
Now, is he a god? I don't know if he's a god.
I mean, he ate a cat, so I don't know, I don't know. But...
I mean, we have to keep him around a while.
A little while.
Hello?
Your water, sir.
And sir, general hoyt...
Tell him I'm not here. Tell him I'll call him back.
Don't put him through.
No, sir!
H-he's in your office.
At this point, our only concern is the asset.
- Do you have it? - Still in the wind, sir.
Well, that won't do.
Yes, sir. I know.
You've known me how long, sir?
Thirteen years.
- Battle of pusan. - Yes, sir.
A man is faithful, loyal, efficient all his life.
All of it... and he is... useful. And he expects...
He has certain expectations in return.
And then he fails, once.
Only once. What does that make him?
Does that make him a failure?
When is a man done, sir? Proving himself?
A good man.
A decent man.
Decent?
A man has the decency not to fuck up.
Now, that's one thing. That's real decent of him.
But the other kind of decency...
It doesn't really matter.
We sell it, but it's an export.
We sell it because we don't use it.
Thirty six hours from now, this entire episode will be over.
And so will you.
Our universe will have a hole in it with your outline.
An you will have moved on to an alternate universe.
A universe of shit.
You will be lost to civilization.
And you will be unborn.
Unmade.
And undone.
So, go get some real decency, son.
And unfuck this mess.
Thirty-six hours.
Thirty-six hours. Well, shit, deliver.
That's what you do. You deliver, right?
Right?!
You'll.
Never know.
Just how much
I've.
Loved
elisa.
What is it, honey?
This isn't good.
I'm gonna call dr. Hoffstetler.
We gotta release him tonight, honey.
I'll come back and help you.
He's coming out.
Ah, fuck.
Sir, if you don't mind me saying, you...
You don't look so well.
Shut up.
Can you smell that? I mean...
I think it's your fingers, they're they're...
black.
There he is.
Doctor fucking shit-bird.
Oh, there's no call for cursing, sir.
Get out of the car, I'm taking it.
- This is my car. - Get the fuck out.
Out of my car?
Did I stutter?
Strickland! Thank god!
You were speaking russian.
Bob.
- What's your name? - Hoffstetler.
No, no. Don't lie. You don't need to.
You took a bullet to the gut.
You're dead.
I need the names, ranks, and
location of the entire.
Strike team?
The ones who took the asset!
This candy. It's cheap candy. B-but I love it.
Ever since I was a kid.
Now some folks favor more sophisticated snacks.
Nougat center and all that fu-fu shit.
But not me, bob.
This is it for me.
Now, sometimes if I'm feeling anxious...
I bite right into it.
But mostly...
I take my time.
I make it last.
Names, ranks, and location of the strike team.
Names! Ranks! Now!
No names.
No ranks.
They...
They just clean.
All right, brewster, I'm gonna fix you dinner,
And then I'm gonna run out for a
little while and help a friend.
- Help with what? - Help a friend.
Zelda.
Door.
Well, you could help me and answer the door, brewster.
You're sittin' right here just ten feet away from it!
My back's achin' me, woman. Now move!
Your back. Your back. Always your back.
Mr. strickland?
What are you doing here?
- Who's that man, zelda? - Where is he?
- What are you talking about? - Where'd you take him?
- Zelda. - What are you talking about?
I-I don't...
The thing...
In the lab.
Where is it?
- Listen, fella... - sit down!
I'm sorry, sir, if-if-
I knew anything, I would surely tell you.
That story about samson.
I never told you how it ends.
After the philistines torture him...
And blind him...
Samson asks god for the strength he needs.
And at the last minute, he's spared.
And the lord gives him his strength back.
One last time.
And he holds...
The columns of the temple with his powerful arms.
And he crushes them.
And he brings the whole building down on the philistines.
He dies.
But he gets every single one of those motherfuckers.
That is his will!
Now, do you know what that particular story means?
For us, delilah?
It means if you know something you're not telling me,
You're gonna tell me.
Either before...
Or after...
I bring this particular temple...
Down upon our heads.
Gal stole that thing right out the lab.
Whatever it is.
Mute girl took it.
I heard my wife talkin' on the phone about it.
Thank you very much, mr. Fuller for your assistance.
What have you done?
- Zelda. - I gotta warn her.
He's going after her.
You will do no such thing, woman.
Why you worryin' about her?
She broke the law.
Shut up, brewster.
You shut up!
For years, you don't talk.
Now you can't shut your mouth.
Damn you, brewster.
You wouldn't understand.
Couldn't understand. Not if you tried your whole life.
- Hello? - Giles, is that you?
- Yes. - Okay, put elisa on the phone.
Zelda.
Elisa, honey...
Make a sound in the phone if you can hear.
Okay, good.
He's comin' for you.
You gotta go now and you gotta take that thing with you.
What? Elisa?!
Dammit.
We have to go.
Where are you?
Where the fuck are you?!
I do not fail.
I deliver.
Elisa!
Elisa.
No!
Fuck.
You are a god.
If I told you about her...
What would I say?
That they lived happily ever after?
I believe they did.
That they were in love?
That they remained in love?
I'm sure that's true.
But when I think of her...
Of elisa...
The only thing that comes to mind is a poem...
Whispered by someone in love...
Hundreds of years ago...
Unable to perceive the shape of You...
"I find you all around me.
"Your presence fills my eyes
"with your love...
"it humbles my heart...
For you are everywhere."
要是我同你说起
如果我
我该告诉你些什么呢
我想
我是否该告诉你那段
发生在很久以前
在正义统治的最后那段时日里
或者和你说说这个地方
一个海边的小城市
远离尘嚣
或者　我不知道
我会和你说说她吗
那个哑巴公主
或者我只需要告知你
事实的真相
关于爱与失落的故事
以及那
想要摧毁这一切的怪物
我有罪
我冒犯了上帝
我罪孽深重　黑德克大人
说来听听
我对祭祀仪式有所怀疑
我不想爬楼梯
劳埃德小姐　如果要睡觉
就得上楼去啊
被警报声吵醒了吗
那是巧克力工厂失火了
你能闻到吗
噢　烧焦的可可味儿
人生　祸福难测
噢　我亲爱的孩子
如果不是你照顾我　我估计会日益消瘦
我这个远近闻名的饿汉
看看这个
在楼梯上跳的　是踢踏舞
那个真难
卡格尼跳过　不一样但是很美
我也要这样跳
好啊
- 准备好了吗　- 好了
来咯
啊
看　你学得真快
埃莉莎
下次你来交房租的时候
留下来看圣经电影吧　好吗
我这里有两张免费的票
你可以带你的邻居贾尔斯来　他是个好人
圣经电影和喜剧　没人会来影院看　对吧
那　我额外赠送爆米花和苏打水
噢　不　布尔加斯　那里是两个S
能不能行
狂欢节　有两个S　两个S
全体人员　请注意
12区已调整至a-c级别
埃莉莎
快点　都到我了
你以后得准时到
嘿　你干嘛呢
- 不要插队　哑巴　- 别瞎说话
我帮她占了位置
要是我被通报了　我一定会来找你和那个哑巴的
那你就来吧　尤兰达
那你来吧
啊
我的脚要痛死了
出门前　我给布鲁斯特做了香肠薄饼
天呐　他全吃光了
没说谢谢　也没说好吃　连看都没看我
男人沉默起来就像一座坟墓
但如果他说点奉承话
那他堪比莎士比亚
然后我就屁颠颠的回去给他做早餐
鸡蛋　熏肉　黄油面包
我连面包上的黄油都给那个男人涂好了
两面都涂了　把他当亲儿子养
但他连句谢谢都没有
你肯定会心怀感激
因为你是一个受过教育的人
但是我的布鲁斯特　我为他所做的一切
仅仅是异性相吸
都好长时间没有工作了
搞什么鬼
卢
你们能不能把垃圾丢进垃圾桶里
垃圾桶用来干嘛的
有意思　用来当摆设的
好了　对不起　泽尔达
我不知道他们在做什么
这帮天杀的就是瞎忙活
泽尔达
- 别唠叨个不停　- 是　先生
而且　不准在此亵渎神灵
对不起　弗莱明先生
宣布一个事情
今天　我们t-4将迎来一支新团队和研究对象
这是来自我们的兄弟实验室的
罗伯特　霍夫斯特勒博士
我不想强调
或者夸大说辞
但这可能是目前为止
这座实验室里最敏感的研究了
- 旅途愉快吗　- 还行
- 这里的安保是谁　-请稍等
安保　谁是安保
先生　欢迎来到t-4
我是弗莱明　安保主管
有任何问题您都可以找我
从现在开始　由我接管这里
让他们都出去
帮我把舱体移到压缩机上
这里　这里
把它放在这里
我们需要立即给它加压
埃莉莎　埃莉莎
快来
上帝　这个地方到底在干什么啊
你刚刚看到了吗
是的　我戴了假发　怎么样
噢　小心　有车
这是遮秃假发　法语词汇
这可是永久的
坦塔罗斯逃脱不了死亡的命运
因为树枝上的果实
他总也触及不到
溪流的水位
只要他弯腰就会下降
现在用于比喻那些可望不可即的
比如那些诱人的馅饼
谢谢　一定要再次馆谷歌
是的　早餐吃馅饼　相信我
嘿　伙计　欢迎来到迪克西餐馆
我以前在这见过你　对吗
是的　事实上我是这里的常客了
来点酸橙派吗
是的　是的　两个打包
你别管　拜托了
呃　这味道真是好极了
这可能不利于健康　但我钟意的事都是这样
不　不　这是一个非常好的派　关键是酸橙
你不会就是
那个著名的迪克西　道格本人吧
不　馅饼由卡车运输到全国各地
他们称之为连锁经营
噢
他们给我们配卡车司机　招牌
那个馅饼男孩　是我们的吉祥物
我可不那样说话　我是渥太华来的
不会吧
我买了
美味的馅饼(美味的小尤物)
那个
呃　那个小男孩　他是意大利人吗
估计是的
太机智了
一定要再次光顾
要再次光顾
你觉得他是那个意思吗
他在暗示我　你　你听到了
这馅饼太脏了
不要吐出来
下次　我们试试别的口味
嗯
那我们等下再吃
现在是东部时间上午6点
天空渐亮
一股凉爽的北风穿过
成群的黑人
聚集在
噢　赶紧换台
我不想看到那个
不想看也不想听
这个好　这个好
噢　看贝蒂
如此年轻貌美
如果回到过去
回到我18岁的时候
那个时候的我一无所知
如果给自己一点建议
我会说
珍爱牙齿　大胆做爱
还有很多
噢不　不　这是个很好的建议
你看下这个
你看
这个国家最优秀的一群人
上个厕所　尿到到处都是
唔　唔　唔
天花板上都有小便的斑点
你说他们是怎么尿的
他们要多大的便池才够啊
他们肯定私底下在练习
我们布鲁斯特
没人说他很优秀
但是
他也能有个70%的时候尿准便池
- 不好意思　先生　-不　不　没事的
继续吧
你们两个聊得很开心啊
肯定是在聊悄悄话
不用理我
埃莉莎
别碰那个
那个可爱的小东西是来自阿拉巴马的问候
模制手柄设计
低电流的高压电棍
我是斯特里克兰　负责安保
弗莱明就是安保
哈
不　不　男人需要洗手
获得满足前或者在那之后
通过这件事可以分析一个男人
要是他前后都洗手
说明他性格软弱
女士们
和你们聊天十分愉快
长得矮的人都很卑鄙
我从来没有遇到过
各方面都很好的矮子
不　先生
他们都是耍阴招的卑鄙小人
估计是下面空气的原因
缺少氧气什么的
嗯
救命　他流血了
来人啊
快走　快走
你觉得是苏联人闯进来了
我不觉得　如果是苏联人
杜安的肉饼都不会放过他们
有两枪　你听到了吗
好吧　三枪
还有尖叫声
上帝　这个地方发生了什么
你们两个　跟我来
现在吗　弗莱明先生
能不能让我们先吃饭
马上
哦　老天爷　真是摊上麻烦了
摊上大麻烦了
给你们20分钟的时间
把这里打扫干净
大概就这些　20分钟
这么多血　这里到底怎么了
尿我都能搞定
屎也不在话下
但是血　额
我和血八字不合
这里　亲爱的　帮我把它擦干
我们赶快把这里搞定吧
那是薯条吗
噢
是手指啊
我知道了　是两根手指
行了行了　赶紧拿开　你在这里等着
我去喊弗莱明先生
那些手指在哪
手指呢
不　我相信你　亲爱的　你确定它还活着吗
因为我曾经在嘉年华帐篷里看到过美人鱼
其实那就是只猴子
缝了条鱼尾巴　真骗到我了
好了　我道歉
我快要交稿了
你知道吗
玉米片是用于防止自慰的
但并不奏效
噢　艾丽丝　费伊开始了
她是个超级巨星　超级
有一天　她受够了
娱乐圈的那些屁事和潜规则
就潇洒地离开了那个圈子
铛铛
当个垃圾看看
也还不错　是吧
你吃完饭就去睡觉　休息下
等我拿到报酬
我们就去买馅饼
不　不给你买　我自己吃
你就吃你喜欢的
祝我好运
绿色
他们想让果冻画成绿色
- 之前跟我说的是红色啊　- 新想法
大势所趋　用绿色吧
他们还想让这一家子　看起来更高兴
- 更快乐　- 嗯
这位父亲看起来像
解锁了传教士体位那样高兴
贾尔斯
他们想要哪种高兴呢
客户本想要的是照片　我说服了他们
很遗憾　这是一幅好作品
没错　我觉得这是我最好的作品之一
你现在靠什么度日
- 你喝酒吗　- 不
滴酒不沾　真的
那你离开克莱恩　桑德斯公司之后　找到工作了吗
你说我被你们辞退后
我们先不谈这个
我想回来　伯尼
再说吧
先做好手头的工作
干得漂亮
埃莉莎
你在这儿做什么
哦　打扫是吧
听着　宝贝
"扶腰撒尿"先生要见我们
泽尔达　D　富勒
泽尔达　你们认识多久了
大概十年了　先生
你没有兄弟姐妹吗
没有　先生
对于你们这种人来说倒是不常见啊
我妈妈生下我后
就死了
那D代表什么
达丽拉　先生
在圣经上找到的名字
达丽拉　她背叛了参孙
骗他入睡　借机剃光了他的头发
腓力斯人对他百般折辱
剜去他的双眼
我想我妈妈没能深刻理解这本好书
而你
埃莉莎　埃斯波西托
埃斯波西托不是孤儿院的意思吗
噢　来自帕特南的悲惨孤儿院啊
他们在河边　确切说在水里找到了她
是你找到了我的手指
噢
谢谢
在手术室里待了三个小时
他们重塑了我的第一根指骨
缝合了我的肌腱
不知道能不能好起来
还有点芥末沾在上面
- 一个纸袋子　- 当时我们只有那个来装
她不能说话　所以我来回答
她不能　她是聋子吗
是哑巴　先生
她说她可以听见
噢　你脖子上的伤疤
就是它们损害了你的声带　对吧
她说从她小时候就有了
谁会那样对一个孩子
这个世界真是罪恶
对吧　达丽拉
好了　来说说之前的事儿
你打扫了实验室然后出去了
关在里面的那个东西　是个耻辱
泽尔达　你知道什么是耻辱吗
比较讨厌的东西
没错　我把那个
肮脏的东西
从南美的淤泥里一路拖到这里
一路上相处得并不好
现在　你可能会认为
那个东西像个人
都是用两条腿走路是吗
但是　我们是凭上帝的模样创造出来的
你们难道认为那东西是上帝的样子吗
先生　我不知道上帝长什么样
泽尔达　他像一个人类　比如我这样的
或者你这样
我想可能会更像我一点
好了　先这样吧
霍伊特将军　谢谢你的回电
- 好些了吗　-是的　长官　好多了
- 吃了止痛药　- 你没了两根手指吗
是的　两根　他咬断了我两根手指
但是我的拇指　食指和中指都还在
你能这样说　肯定就会没事的
当然　将军　恭候您的到来
那东西还得您来做决定
果味馅饼期待您的光顾
巴尔的摩市中心新开了三家店
前途光明
休息一下吧
九点半来接我
九点半　好的长官
迪克西　道格斯　美味的馅饼
我回来了
给你做了一个煎蛋卷
-嘿　爸爸　我告诉你-没有薄煎饼吗
我找了很多个箱子
但没找到平底锅
我告诉你
所以给你做的是奶酪和花菜蛋卷
你现在怎么样　疼吗
-有点　吃了药好多了-我告诉你
- 什么　- 我们在新学校那儿
埋了一个时间囊　我想问问你
我们以后会不会都有
- 飞行背囊　- 会有的
噢　公交车来了
这可是美国
- 爸爸再见　- 爸爸再见
吃完煎蛋卷后　好好洗手
洗完上楼来　亲爱的
我有点喜欢这儿了　孩子们特别钟意这个草坪
并且　从这儿到华盛顿只有半小时的路程
但这里还是巴尔的摩　伊莱恩　这地方不招人待见
你知道我在想什么吗
我在想　我需要一辆新车
你需要一辆新车　是吗
一辆凯迪拉克怎么样　长官
理查德
噢
噢　理查德
喔　噢
噢
宝　宝贝
宝贝　你
你　你的手在流血
别说话
安静　安静
啊　嗯　别说话
航空学博士莱文森　航空学博士莱文森
- 在窗户上　- 什么
雀
仍在窗上筑巢
- 而鹰叼走自己的猎物　- 什么
埃莉莎　快点
快点　姑娘
泽尔达你又这样
一边儿待着去
噢
哟
嘿　泽尔达　来一根不
- 吸烟有害健康　杜安
- 没错　但我挺健康的
确实有害健康
来吧　埃莉莎　就一根
来来来
不用担心那个摄像头　我们休息时就把它抬上去
- 额　- 这是一个盲区
弗莱明　我得在这儿做点事
可以帮我拿一下麦当劳吗
你想我了哈
我带了一个小点心
你害怕这个　是吧
吉　从此刻起你要习惯它
你又来了　发出那种讨厌的噪音
是你在哭吗　啊　是不是
你受伤了
还是说
你生气了
或者你想再咬我一口　来啊
哈啊
你真敢啊
我说　你在求我吗
那见鬼的声音
是我听过最烦心的噪音
转接沃尔特斯上校
沃尔特斯上校　内线电话
埃莉莎
- 霍伊特将军　欢迎您的到来
万事俱备　你能来真是太好了
- 见到你很开心　孩子　- 非常荣幸
上帝保佑啊
比我想得大得多啊
丑陋无比
你知道吗　亚马逊的野蛮人
把他当神供着
现在倒不像一个神了
长官　他们都是些野蛮人
他们会扔一些贡品进去
像花啊水果啊之类的垃圾
他们还试图用弓箭阻止我们钻油井
真是异想天开
他在流血
发生了什么
它就是个畜生　霍夫斯德勒　只管驯服它就行
小伙子　我们抓到了怎样一个怪物啊
长官　这个生物
他可以轮流使用两个完全独立
的呼吸系统
- 泥鳅也可以做到啊　- 不不不
听着　如果你想把人送入太空
他必须要忍受
普通人体所不能忍受的各种环境
这能增加我们与苏联竞争的胜算
它离了水还能呼吸多久
长官　事实是我们
不太了解这个东西
我们都知道　苏联人很想要它
那些杂种们
我们任其送了一条狗进太空
然后我们嘲笑他们
接下来发生的事情你们也知道　他们送人进了太空
卫星绕着我们的星球转　天知道他们在搞什么鬼
接下来轮到谁笑了　赫鲁晓夫
我们任其送狗进太空
他笑着又送了一个小子进太空
他又笑着在古巴投了导弹
我们学到了什么
长官　我们得把他放到水里
看这些科学家倒像是艺术家了
他们爱上了自己的玩物
看这里　在中间
这家伙有一个厚实的关节软骨
将主肺和次肺分开了
鲍勃　我说得对吗
是这样　但是我们
能够决定
它让X光
理论上是的　但是
- 我们有很多方法　- 我相信如果我们想
打败苏联　就得解剖这个东西
不　不
- 把他大卸八块　然后深入研究　- 不
不　这违背了我们的初衷
长官　求您了　他昏过去了
把他放进罐子里加压
霍伊特将军
不论怎样您都不能杀他
小伙子　数数这些星
整整五颗星
意味着我有权任意处置这怪物
如果你想汇报研究成果　我会听下去
但是到最后
由我做决定
把那个东西解剖了
仔细研究然后结束它
然后给你自己放个假好好休息　斯特里克兰
- 你做得很棒　- 谢谢你　长官
快点结束这个任务
当然　长官
帮他逃脱　你在说什么
当然不可以
这是违法的
或许谈论这件事也犯法了
他很孤独
难道说
不论何时我们走进一家中餐馆
你都想把水槽里的每条鱼都救下来吗
就算他很孤独又怎样
人生来孤独
你见过的最悲伤的东西
你是这样说的　没错吧　你刚刚这样说
你把它称作是一个东西　东西　是个怪物
我能理解你
冷静
拜托　冷静
好好好　我说给你听
我是谁
我张开嘴
如他一般
却无法发声
什么造就了我
我自身所有
我所经历
将我引至这里
带我遇见他
看　你刚刚用的是　他
这是个
啊　你刚刚打了我
埃莉莎　放开我
我算是看清楚了　你以前从来没有打过我
当他看着我
他看我的方式
他不知道
我的残缺
或者
我是多么的
不完整
他看着我
只是因为
我是我
他每次
每天
看见我
都很开心
但是现在
我要么
救他
要么看他死
好吧
我要走了
我得走了啊
埃莉莎　别这样
听我说　听我说就好
我现在得走了
我现在必须离开　因为
埃莉莎　这对我非常重要
这是我再次得到的机会
我很抱歉　但是我必须走了
我的天啊
当我回来的时候
我们就别再谈这事了
埃莉莎　那
好吧
我们是什么　你和我
我们什么也不是
什么也不是　我们什么也做不了
对不起
但这一切　这一切就是
天啊　它甚至不是人
天啊
怎么
贾尔斯
我一直在等你
- 我知道　抱歉　- 没事
去里面谈
其实你直接寄过来就行了
不　我想亲自展示给你们看
我认为这是我最好的作品之一
这也改成绿色了
只是　现在不是时候
我们迟些再谈
呃　嗯　行　没问题
什么时候才是时候呢　伯尼
那是你画的
是
哇
你很棒
显然　还没到达照片的逼真度
但还是很棒　对吗
反正我可做不到
来　我请你吧
请我么
像你这样的客人十分少见
你看上去　很有教养
我喜欢和你聊天
事实上　我
我之所以到这来是想
和我聊天　以及
这个馅饼绝了　对吧
对　对
这不是酸橙派　但也很好吃的
我没有同事
呃
我最好的朋友也不是健谈的人
你瞧　那就是这个工作的一部分　就像
酒保一样
你给他们做馅饼　你也会倾听他们的烦恼
你才能去了解他们
我也想多了解你
你想干嘛　老家伙
哦　呃
喂　不行　你们不能坐在吧台上
你们只能打包带走　不能坐那儿
你们要吃什么　就下单　然后打包带走
但这没人呀　这个吧台都没坐人
今天一天都被包下了　不准坐这儿
再次光顾　听见了吗
你没必要用那种口气跟他们说话
你也走吧
而且不许再来了　这里只接待亲友
没人理我了
你是唯一能和我聊天的人了
好吧
不管是啥
你都要去做
所以
告诉我　我能帮你做什么吧
所有希望都已凋零
都随着春日而消逝了　走吧
凯迪拉克德维尔　史上最好的汽车
V8发动机　390马力　就像崭新的美元大钞一样
- 我就随便看看　- 我也随便说说
广播收音　配备空调　电动车窗　电子刹车
电动方向盘　电动座椅调整
还可更换豪华内饰
有143种可供选择　你看
这就是行走的泰姬陵啊
嗯
我不太喜欢这个绿色
不　这可不是绿色　朋友　这是水鸭色
- 好吧　看上去就是绿色　- 但你看　这不是绿色
这可是限量款　有12层喷漆
纯手工抛光　全镀铬装饰
全美五分之四的成功人士都选择凯迪拉克
是吗　这就是大势所趋
您一看就是能掌控未来的人
- 什么　- 未来啊
您就是未来的主宰
您才配拥有这辆车
哇
长官　这车真棒啊
这是
要我说　开着它的感觉一定棒极了
这真是个好看的绿色啊
是水鸭色
水鸭色
- 明天　- 怎么
- 我做千层肉饼　- 是吗
专门给你做　多加点葡萄干
清晨五点　我驾车去卸货台
那时候他们正在换班
我有多少时间
五分钟　我会记得的
五点　五分钟　五分钟
再对一下　你负责移动摄像头
我再和你对下手表的时间
就像电影里拍的那样
天啊　我真为你骄傲
天啊　你一点也不害怕
什么　你很害怕
别说了　我都快吓死了
我觉得这是我最好的作品之一了
迈克尔　帕克　听起来像是
老实人的名字　简单粗暴
对　51岁
54岁
你能不能别这么直接
那就57岁　吧
我还是戴个假发吧　我能混过去的
我穿这个还是
哦　去　去　去　下去
或者是这件　这件
穿着就像　我是个有工作的人一样
但这件　这件
搭配上奶油色的领带
就传达出随意而时髦的感觉
所以　你喜欢这件　我也同意
我想我们准备好了
斯特里克兰先生
莎莉　你能打给埃斯波西托小姐来清理一下吗
你说　我也搞不懂自己
你又不是大美女　但
伤脑筋
我时时想着你
你说你的世界是无声的　是完全说不出话
还是你也能发出呻吟声呢
浅浅的呻吟
我只想让你知道
我不介意你的疤痕
我也不介意你不能说话
你这样跪在我面前的样子
我很喜欢
很喜欢
让我性奋
我想我也能让你叫出声来
亲爱的　你还好吗
快点啦　我想早点回家
我的脚痛死了
我们得延迟计划了
先敲门再进来
我有急事
出去　敲门
我再让你进来说话
这是礼貌　你要遵守礼节
进来
我
你能给我关下门吗
这样才对　说吧
我需要更多时间
别让你的挫败感
还有胜负欲
我没有胜负欲
我只是不想毁掉一件复杂而美丽的事物
这东西要是死了　你能学到知识　我也能离开
离开这儿　在新的地方安身
和我的家人定居在一个美丽的　真正的城市
这种生物很聪明
能说话
能理解感情
苏联人和朝鲜人不也是吗
我们不也把他们灭了吗
记住　这不是动物保护协会
我也不想再在这个
鬼地方多呆一会了
你呢
鲍勃
你想在这呆着吗
不　我不想
你还在等什么
你有见到埃莉莎吗
快点　泽尔达
是你移动了卸货台的摄像头吗
你要带他去那儿吗
从隧洞出去是吗
真聪明
是谁指使你这么做的
这种水必须保持在百分之五到八的盐度
用食盐就行
每三天就往他的水里加一些这个
原蛋白的食物是不可少的
五分钟内　我会在卸货台和你汇合
我去断电　你做好准备
斯特里克兰长官
还有12小时就要进行活体解剖了
我　我需要您在这上面签字
停车
你叫　迈克尔　帕克
君子行不更名
你是疯了吗
别这么做　埃莉莎
别这么做
那是　那是什么车
呃　我也不确定　是洗衣房的车吗
但　也不是在这个时候来
长官
- 在卸货台和我汇合　- 长官
- 长官　有何吩咐　- 快去叫人
先生　从车里出来
天啊　我最不会处理这种事了
快出来
我不会再重复一遍
- 天啊　别开枪　- 出来
天啊　别开枪
你还在等什么　我们没时间了
快出来
我们得走了　快点
哦　你个蠢女人　我们会下地狱的
快点　推
推呀
推啊
我发誓我不是故意的
我总是不会弄这些机械化的东西
什么
她在卸货台等你
- 快点　去啊　- 好　我这就去
那是谁　他刚好像杀了人
噢
噢　天啊　天啊
我们准备好了吗　真准备好了吗
他真美丽
是我撞的吗
我真不会开车
快点　快点
不
盐　你说什么　盐
埃莉莎
以色列的爆竹
有闻到镁的味道吗
俄罗斯人不喜欢犹太人
却不得不用他们生产的玩意
他们是怎么进来的
呃　假身份和假牌照
之类的
他们还把卸货台的监控头掉了方向　先生
先别传出消息　我们有一天时间来处理
我已经上报了
- 你上报了　- 事件一发生我就　就
斯特里克兰先生
怎么了　莎莉
先生　霍伊特将军打电话来
斯特里克兰　那东西就是我们的太空狗
- 你知道的　- 先生　我会把它抓回来的
我不　不能再有负面想法了　先生
你感觉很好是吗
我有信心　能把它抓回来
你能做到的　你会做到的
为我那么做好吧　孩子　为了我
这是你计划放走他的日子吗
十号
万一没雨呢
水道会怎么样
行吧
那是什么
我看看
那是给我的
不错　你就这么保持着吧
装作什么也不知道
万一我被问到就只能求上天保佑了
我不擅长撒谎啊
骗布鲁斯特我倒拿手
为了维系这段婚姻我撒了很多谎
全体注意　请出示你们的身份证和门禁卡
天啊　这是
看你让我们陷入什么麻烦里
依我看　我们要对付的是一个经过高度训练的组织　先生
我想到的　或许是
特种部队或之类的
你是说　苏联特种部队
可能是　我　我是说　他们都是受过训练的
也有资金支持　精英组织
高效　冷酷　精确
整个过程用时不到五分钟　长官
我保守估计　这是个至少有十个人的
突击部队
你一直都是一个人吗
你有过其他人吗
你知道你身上发生了什么事吗　你知道吗
因为我不知道　我不知道自己发生了什么
我不知道
我看镜子时　唯一能认出的
只有这双眼睛
在一张沧桑的老脸上
有时候我会觉得
自己生不逢时
我们都被这乱世所遗弃了
安保系统已升至最高等级
请准备出示你的身份和门禁卡
长官　找到她们了
泽尔达　埃莉莎
看起来你们在事发前就下班了
但例行公事
如果你们知道任何有关线索
你们有义务向我报告
哪怕看起来微不足道的细节
微不足道意思是不重要的
我没注意到任何不正常的事情
或者微不足道的事情
我的脚一直很痛
你呢
她什么也没注意到
霍夫斯特勒　霍夫斯特勒博士
你们有看见他出入实验室吗
他在那工作　不是吗
我意思不是工作性质的　在做些不寻常的事情
微不足道的事吗
没有　长官
我在干嘛
竟然在向你们询求帮助
倒垃圾的
扫厕所的
你们走吧　出去
你在对我说什么
她在说什么
我没看见
她说　谢谢您
下一个
你昨晚没来看我
前天晚上也是
我很抱歉　但既然现在
我不用成天工作
卡洛认为我需要在晚上陪她
要是你在晚上陪她
我什么时候才能见你
看来我们只能做一件事了
志愿者
不不不不
我想早点回家
最近布鲁斯特脾气很差
我的天
你躲在女更衣室里
干什么
他们可能在监视我　这里没有摄像头
不错的理由啊
要是你撞到我们在换衣服呢
我需要知道他是否安好
- 他很好　- 什么时候放他走
很快
当通海水道被雨水灌满的时候
有需要就找我
尽快放他走
她说什么
她说　你是个好人　霍夫斯特勒博士
我的名字是迪米特里
很荣幸认识你们
嘿　哑巴　有电话找你　很紧急
先别管我　我没事
相信我　我没事
他把潘多拉吃了　不是他的错
他毕竟有野性的
我们不能要求太多
埃莉莎　快去找他
快去
去吧
你很幸运
我一直尽力保持清醒
但是　我还是老了
他还好吗　你确定
你去哪
别
好吧　不不　别跟猫咪玩了　别
别跟猫咪玩
我没生气　我没有
这是你干的　但没关系
我觉得这有点不卫生
可以了
这家伙挺有意思
请准备出示你的身份证和门禁卡
你找我
调查怎么样了
我已经有些眉目了
是吗
那真挺好
你在加尔维斯顿加入我们的
你之前在哪工作　霍夫斯特勒
博士
- 什么　- 霍夫斯特勒博士
这是礼貌
我在威斯康星大学麦迪逊校区
对　你放弃了
终身教授的职位　对吧
为了我们　放弃了一切
我猜想
你现在已经打算离开我们了吧
如果那个生物没有被找到的话
那你怎么想　你觉得我们能找到它吗
你说你已经有点眉目了
我确实有
亲爱的　你在笑什么
别这副表情
你们发生什么了
怎么会发生
他怎么可能
怎么做到的
他有吗
我的天啊
永远别相信男人
即使他下面看上去空无一物
你按的铃吗
彼特　我刚报名了人类学
我们要去
南美的亚马逊丛林上课
南美　我天呐
那你可得起个大早了
那地方太远了
不　彼特　我们要呆在那里
我们吗
不　你不会不来吧
试试吉利丁果冻
你会喜欢它的
爸爸　我们能看伯南扎的牛仔吗
那部片子太暴力了
你知道我今天在想什么吗
我们该给孩子一只宠物狗
怎么回事啊
水都灌进我的剧院了
有四个顾客都买票了　我还得退钱给人家
可能是个管道问题　我会处理的
你修不好就别住了
我会修好的
埃莉莎
上帝啊
我在擦我的头发
我的头发
还有我的手臂
那个伤口　就像从没有过一样　看
你说过
他被供奉为神灵
他是上帝吗　我不知道他是不是
毕竟他吃过一只猫　我真不知道
我们得让他多留一段时间
只要一小段
喂
你的水　长官
还有长官　霍伊特将军
告诉他我不在　我一会打给他
别把他接进来
不是的　长官
他已经在你的办公室了
在这个节骨眼上　我们当务之急就是那个研究对象
- 你找到它了吗　- 还没有　长官
这不太妙啊
是　长官　我知道
你认识我多久了　长官
十三年
- 釜山战役　- 是的长官
一个男人　毕生虔诚　忠心　高效
他还很能干　并期待着
他当然想着获得对等的回报
然后他失败了　一次
只有一次　那导致了什么
这会使他成为一个失败者吗
当这个男人完成任务　证明自己
是个好人
一个体面可敬的人
体面
一个体面的人可不会搞砸事情
那是一种体面　一种真正的体面可敬
但其他类型的体面
就没什么用了
我们摈弃它　更像是自我提升
因为我们不需要它
三十六小时后一切都结束了
包括你
你将从我们的世界里消失
你会去另一个世界
一个糟糕透顶的世界
你会在那片文明里迷失
你的痕迹会被抹除
一干
二净
去追求些真正的体面吧　小伙子
还有收拾好这个烂摊子
三十六小时
三十六小时　去送货
你就干这活　送货的
对吧
你永远
不会知道
我有
多么
爱你
埃莉莎
怎么了　亲爱的
这不太妙啊
我去给霍夫斯特勒博士打电话
亲爱的　我们今天必须放他走
我会过来帮你
他要出来了
该死的
长官　恕我直言
你看起来不太好
闭嘴
你闻到了吗　我是说
我觉得你的手指　它们
变黑了
他来了
该死的狗屁博士
没必要咒骂　长官
你出去　我要用你的车
- 这是我的车　- 快给我滚出去
从我的车里
我表达得不够清楚吗
太好了　斯特里克兰
你在说俄语
鲍勃
- 你的名字是什么　- 霍夫斯特勒
不不　别撒谎　你不需要
你肚子中弹了
你马上要死了
告诉我突击队所有人的
姓名　军衔和地址
突击队
那些带走研究对象的人
这种糖　很便宜　但我爱吃
从我小时候就开始
现在很多人偏爱那些更精细的零食
牛扎糖　还有那些杂七杂八的
但我不是　鲍勃
我就爱吃这个
有时当我觉得紧张的时候
我就大嚼一通
但大多数情况
我会细细品尝
直到最后一点
突击队的姓名　军衔还有地址
姓名和军衔
没有姓名
没有军衔
他们
他们身家清白（清洁工）
布鲁斯特　我给你做晚饭
然后我要出去一小会
去帮朋友一个忙
- 帮什么　- 就是帮忙呗
泽尔达
门
也许你可以帮我去开下门
你就坐在离门十尺的地方
我的背很痛啊　女人　快让开
你的背　你的背　永远都是你的背
斯特里克兰先生
你来这干什么
- 这个男人是谁　泽尔达　- 他在哪
- 你在说什么　- 你把他带到哪里去了
- 泽尔达　- 你在说什么
我不明白
在实验室的
那个东西
在哪
- 听着　老兄　- 坐　下
不好意思　先生　如果
我知道什么　我肯定会告诉你
我还没告诉你
参孙故事的结局
在腓力斯人对他严刑拷打
还把他弄瞎后
参孙向上帝祈求力量
在最后一刻　他变的气急败坏
但就在那时上帝给予了他所要的力量
最后一刻
而后他用他有力的手
抓住神庙里的大柱
他把它们捏碎
整座神庙都塌了　砸死了腓力斯人
虽然他也死了
但他让那些杂碎都为他陪了葬
那就是他的愿望
你知道这个故事影射什么吗
放在我们身上　达丽拉
它影射了　你知道些内情但却没告诉我
你会告诉我
无论是
在我
拆掉你家之前
还是之后
那个哑巴从实验室偷了那个东西
不管那是什么
是哑女把它带走了
我之前听到我老婆在电话里说这件事
万分感谢你　福勒先生
你干了什么
- 泽尔达　- 我得去提醒她
他去找她了
女人　你不许干这种事
你管她干嘛
她犯法了
闭嘴　布鲁斯特
你给我闭嘴
这么多年来你都保持沉默
现在却闭不上嘴了
去你大爷的　布鲁斯特
你永远不明白
再怎么努力也不会明白的　永远
- 喂　- 贾尔斯是你吗
- 是　- 好　帮我叫埃莉莎来
泽尔达
埃莉莎　宝贝
如果听见给我点声音
好的
他来找你了
你现在就得带上他走
什么　埃莉莎
该死的
我们必须得走了
你在哪
你他妈在哪
我没有失败
我送到了
埃莉莎
不
我天
你真的是神
如果我要讲关于她的故事
我该怎么说呢
从此他们永远幸福快乐的生活在一起了
我相信是的
他们相爱
他们永远相爱
我确信这是真的
但当我想到她
想到埃莉莎
我的脑海里只会出现一首诗
那是几百年前
一对爱人的呢喃情话
难以描绘你的形状
你却如水　围绕着我
你的存在
使我眼中满是你的爱意
柔软了我的心
因你无处不在
那是暗号
鹰叼走了自己的猎物
走吧
鲍勃
最近怎么样
我像个傻子一样坐在混凝土块上
等了你一个小时
我们每次都在这个烂餐厅接头
我会换地方的
但是你没有
告诉我们
鲍勃
我是迪米特里
同志
我不是鲍勃
这是什么
迪米特里
解剖学笔记
还有
实验室的布局
也就是研究这家伙的地方
我们抽身所需要的一切
都在这儿了
我会向上头报告的
我们得尽快搞定它
马尔可夫
我认为
这个生物
可能会交流
交流
是的 与我们交流
我有理由相信
他是智慧生物
它能
它能对
语言
音乐做出反应
这些你也能
向上级报告吗
我会的
现在就
开吃吧 迪米特里
他们把这叫做
海鲜
牛排
海鲜牛排套餐
这里的龙虾肉处理得正好
滋啦滋啦的
就是
有点软
有点甜
莫斯科不会支持你的计划的
为什么
太冒险了
时间太急
什么
迪米特里 我们只有两个选择
一个是
你想办法推迟计划
至少一周
但他们明天就要动手了
那
只能用
第二个办法
以色列 爆竹
你把它装在保险盒上
能断电五到十分钟
监控失效 你也没有了阻碍
然后
将这个注射到它身上
给它注射
杀了它
毁掉它
你还好吧
我来到这个国家
尽我所能地学习
既是因为爱国
也因为我热爱科学
这里还有很多东西需要我们学习
我们不需要学习
我们只要让美国人
无处可学
请进
你的撤退文件
快准备好了
但首先 我有个问题问你
您说
你们要不要来点
黄油蛋糕
好啊
那个东西
你给它注射后
尸体怎么处理的
我有点好奇
我对它进行了解剖
没发现任何价值
正如列宁说的
变质之鱼 毫无价值
列宁
说过这话吗
蛋糕不错
你这儿有牛奶吗
或许
可能
可能是
你记错了吧
等我们的回音
不会很久的
撤退
已被批准
四十八小时后
老地方见
四十八小时吗
四十八小时
雨下得真大啊
今天不说暗号吗
不要 同志 不要
不要
求你了
电影《小上校》
基督教电影《路得记》成功回归 狂欢节
天主教狂欢节 正确写法只有一个S
坦塔罗斯：宙斯的儿子 得罪神祇后被打入地狱 饱受折磨
电视上播放伯明翰运动 正驱散黑人示威
歌手 舞蹈家
参孙 达丽拉 圣经人物
下雨/码头
很高兴和你做朋友
每日哲思
生活不过是我们计划的沉船残骸
吃了吗
很美
谢谢
你会说什么
我确定
我很确定
这不是垃圾
我不吃
祝你好运
鸡蛋
为什么不行
他很孤独
特别孤独
说出我打的手语
你根本没听我说
说啊
说出来
说出我打的手语
如果我们
袖手旁观
我们也不配为人
会下雨的
去
死
吧
你
你受伤了
你在流血
你
和我
一起
鸡蛋
你永远
不会
知道
你
和我
一起
不 我不去
我不去